networkfleet.com 2015-12-11

# Verizon | About You - Privacy Policy

###  Verizon is Committed to Protecting Your Privacy

At Verizon, we are committed to maintaining strong and meaningful privacy protections for customers. Our privacy policy is designed to inform you about the information we collect, how we use it, and your options about certain uses of information. Key elements of our full privacy policy are summarized below.

Verizon's privacy policy applies to website visitors and customers of the Verizon family of companies in the United States. Additional privacy practices that apply to FiOS, Verzion Wireless, AOL and hum services are also described in the full policy. Supplemental privacy policies for AOL companies and the services they provide are described in the [AOL privacy policy](http://privacy.aol.com/). In the event of a conflict between the Verizon privacy policy and the AOL privacy policy, the AOL policy will control when you are on an AOL site or using an AOL product or service.  
Read more

###  Information We Collect and How We Use It

Verizon collects and uses information about our customers and website visitors when you interact with us, when you use our products and services, and when you visit our websites.

This information is used to deliver, provide, and repair products or services; establish and maintain customer accounts and billing records; contact you about our products and services and direct offers or promotions to you; monitor website statistics; and manage and protect our networks. Information may also be aggregated or anonymized for business and marketing uses by us or by third parties.

We may also obtain consumer information (such as demographic and interest data) from outside companies who provide such data. We use this data and combine it with other information we have to help us predict customer preferences and direct marketing offers.  
Read more

###  Information Provided to or Used by Third-Party Advertisers

You may see third-party advertisements on some Verizon websites, services, or devices. In some instances, advertisers seek to provide advertising that may be more relevant to your interests. They do this, for example, by placing cookies on your browser and using them to collect information about your visit on our websites. They may combine this information with similar information obtained from other websites. We also may provide third-party advertisers with the ability to target their ads using certain information about customers. This information does not identify you individually. You have choices and may limit the use of your information.  
Read more

###  Information We Share

####  Within the Verizon Family of Companies:

Verizon shares customer information within our family of companies. You can limit our sharing of certain types of customer information, known as Customer Proprietary Network Information, for certain marketing uses.  
Read more

####  Outside the Verizon Family of Companies:

Except in circumstances explained in our Privacy Policy, in privacy policies for specific services, or in agreements with our customers, Verizon does not sell, license or share information that individually identifies our customers with others outside of Verizon who are not doing work on Verizon's behalf without your consent. We may share information with our vendors and partners for business purposes and when necessary for them to perform work on our behalf. Verizon may also share certain non-personal identifiable information with outside companies to assist with the delivery of advertising campaigns or preparing and sharing aggregate business and marketing reports.  
Read more

###  How to Limit the Sharing and Use of Your Information

####  Your Choices

  * ####  Customer Information:

You may choose to opt out of the sharing of specific customer information, within the Verizon family of companies for certain marketing purposes.  
Read more

  * ####  Telemarketing:

You may request to be removed from the Verizon telemarketing lists at any time.  
Read more

  * ####  Marketing Email, Postal Mail and Door-to-Door Calls:

You may opt out of receiving marketing-related emails, text messages, or postal mailings or prevent door-to-door marketing.  
Read more

  * ####  Information Used for Online Advertising:

You have choices about whether certain information collected on websites, including Verizon's, is used to customize advertising based on predictions generated from your visits over time and across different websites.  
Read more

  * ####  Wireless Location Services:

Verizon apps that use location information provide users with choices about controls around the use of this information.  
Read more

  * ####  FiOS TV Services:

Specific privacy protections apply to Verizon's FiOS and other fiber-to-the-premises services.  
Read more

  * ####  Relevant Advertising:

Customers may opt-out of participating in relevant online, mobile and tv advertising programs.  
Read more

  * ####  Business and Marketing Insights:

Verizon Wireless customers may opt-out of allowing Verizon Wireless to use their information to create aggregated business and marketing insights.  
Read more

  * ####  AOL:

You have choices about how AOL uses information. To learn more, visit the [AOL Privacy Policy](http://privacy.aol.com/).

  * ####  Parental Controls:

Age-based content controls are available for Verizon's Internet, Wireless and TV services.  
Read more

###  Information Security

Verizon has technical, administrative and physical safeguards in place to help protect against unauthorized access to, use or disclosure of customer information we maintain.  
Read more

###  Contact Information

If you have questions, concerns or suggestions related to our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact us at:

Verizon Privacy Office  
1300 I Street, NW  
Suite 400 West  
Washington, DC 20005  
Fax: 202-289-6781  
Email: [privacyoffice@verizon.com ](mailto:privacyoffice@verizon.com)

###  Accessing and Updating Your Information

You may correct inaccuracies in your information by calling a customer service representative or by accessing your online account and updating your information.  
Read more

###  Changes to the Privacy Policy

If Verizon elects to use or disclose information that identifies you as an individual in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our policy at the time we collected that information from you, we will give you a choice regarding such use or disclosure by appropriate means, which may include use of an opt-out mechanism.  
Read more

Verizon is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  
Read more

Updated October, 2015

© 2009, 2011-2015 Verizon. All Rights Reserved.
